jobform.com 2004-06-04

# PlanetRecruit: IT, Engineering and Management jobs from the UK's top recruitment agencies - Employment, careers, work

| 

hotonline Limited ("hotonline") is strongly committed to protecting your privacy, and this document sets out our policy on the use of personal data. This privacy policy may be updated from time to time. 

## What information will we collect about you?

  * When you register to use the hotonline website, we will record - your name, address, telephone number, email address, year of birth, sex, current salary level, education level, current and desired location, ideal job description and all other details comprising your curriculum vitae ("CV") submitted by you.
  * We also collect broad demographic data and general "traffic" data to enable us to see which are the most popular areas of our site and to provide you with a more tailored service.

## How your information is used 

  * By marking your CV "private" on the registration form, we may use your personal information for job applications posted on the hotonline website. Your information will not be accessible to third parties who search our database for candidates and will only be distributed to recruitment agencies with whom you have applied for a job.
  * If you do not mark your CV as "private", information contained in your CV will be accessible online to third parties through the hotonline database and your personal information may be provided to third parties for the purpose of finding employment for you.
  * We may email you with information updates, news or promotional material from hotonline from time to time, which you have subscribed to or may be of interest to you.

## Who sees your personal information?

  * Any third party who registers to use the hotonline services and accesses your personal information through the hotonline database (if your CV is not marked "private"), or receives your personal information from hotonline, in order to place you for employment.
  * A copy of your CV may be retained by any third party in their own files or databases, and circulated to other people within their organisation. We are not responsible for the use or privacy of the contents of your CV in such instances.
  * We do not sell or rent out our database of personal information.

## Transfer outside the EEA

  * Personal information comprising your CV may be accessed through the hotonline database by third parties outside the Economic European Area ("EEA").
  * If indicated by your preference of location on the registration form, we may forward your personal information to third parties outside the EEA for the purposes of gaining you employment in such countries.
  * By registering and using the hotonline website, you consent to this transfer.

## Cookies

  * A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, used to store and track information about you.
  * Generally, we use cookies on our website to:
  * remind us who you are and to access your member information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver a better and more personalised service;
  * record searches your have made whilst visiting our site;
  * collect anonymous data for direct marketing and promotional purposes;
  * This site, www.planetrecruit.com, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to: [http://www.engage.com/privacy](http://www.engage.com/privacy/).
  * hotonline also collects Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses. Your IP address is the address your web browser or email application automatically gives to the computer whose web page or email you are trying to access over the Internet.
  * IP addresses may be used for the system administration of our website and to gather broad demographic information, including to:
  * send you the most appropriate employment information based on geographic area or information derived from your IP address, and
  * estimate the total amount of users visiting the hotonline website from various locations.

## Other ways of ensuring your privacy

  * You may amend your personal details at any time or if you wish, remove your CV from the hotonline database. These options are available from the "My hotonline" page of our website.
  * You may unsubscribe to any employment, promotional or marketing information you have subscribed to receive from hotonline at any time, from the "My hotonline" page of our website.
  * To opt out of the Engage anonymous targeted advertising information, go to: [www.engage.com/privacy.](http://www.engage.com/privacy/)

## Contacting hotonline

If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding hotonline or this website, please contact us: 

Email: [recruitmentsupport@hotonline.com](mailto:recruitmentsupport@hotonline.com)

**Mailing Address:**

3 Shortlands

Hammersmith 

London 

W6 8JH
